#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/antwongck (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Game Design
Programming
Game Development

#### Certifications

Diver MENSA

# Anthony, Chung Kit Wong

Development Team Lead at The Bad Nomads

Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur

# Summary

I am a passionate software developer with three years of industry experience in building various systems. I specialize in C++ and have professional experience in many languages including Javascript and Perl. I have also picked up advanced mastery of Git and Regex across my professional experience as well as good code review and test-driven development practices.

# Experience

The Bad Nomads

Development Team Lead

April 2021 - Present (9 months)

Self-employed
Programming Trainer
April 2020 - Present (1 year 9 months)

- Train students of varying programming expertise to write and understand code in a multitude of languages
- Plan syllabus unique to each student to suit their purposes in learning programming
- Work on hand picked mini-projects in tandem with each student to solidify their knowledge they have attained

Streamline Studios Game Developer June 2019 - April 2020 (11 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Worked with an established game studio, CI Games, to release Sniper Ghost Warrior Contracts
- Introduce software development practices and workflow into a budding environment
- Spearhead implementation of code reviews and test cases

- Refactor, add features to, and improve large existing codebases in many client projects, most of which cannot currently be named due to legal reasons
- Develop entirely new features for prototypes within the company, along with architecture planning for said features

Binary.com

Developer

November 2017 - June 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Malaysia

- Constant refactoring of a massive codebase for improved documentation and maintainability
- Introduce new features as required for the platform complete with meaningful test cases
- Review job applicants and proctor candidates in weekly hackathons for recruitment
- Lead weekly inter-department meetings designed for transparency between departments
- Worked in tandem with the UI/UX, Front-End and QA teams to produce the best product for our clients

University of Nottingham

Co-Curricular

October 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 9 months)

Nottingham, United Kingdom

- With approval from the dean, took a Masters module (advanced robotic systems)
- Class representative
- Improvements to state of the art recognition algorithm by oversampling on MNIST and CIFAR-10 datasets

#### C27

Intern

May 2016 - September 2016 (5 months)

Malaysia

- Game designer
- Front-End developer
- Level design
- Built a complete website (absolute-animals.com)

#### **HELP University**

#### Co-Curricular

January 2014 - June 2014 (6 months)

Malaysia

- Founder and president of Table-top Society
- Treasurer of Toastmasters Club
- Freelance tuition teacher

## Education

## University of Nottingham

Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Computer Science · (2015 - 2017)

## **HELP University**

A-Levels, Science · (2013 - 2015)

## Cempaka Schools

SPM, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2007 - 2012)